export const Quizdata1 = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `'星期一' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["xīng qī yī", "xīng qī yì", "xīng qī yí", "xīng qī yǐ"],
        answer: "xīng qī yī"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `'今天' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["jīn tián", "jīn tiān", "jīn diǎn", "jīn diàn"],
        answer: "jīn tiān"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: `'动物' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["dòng wǔ", "dōng wú", "dòng wù", "dǒng wǔ"],
        answer: "dòng wù"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `'学校' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["xuè xiāo", "xuè xiào", "xuè xiǎo", "xué xiào"],
        answer: "xué xiào"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `'知道' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["zhī dào", "zhī dāo", "zhǐ dǎo", "zhí dào "],
        answer: "zhī dào"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: `'饕餮' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["tāo tiè", "tāo tián", "tāo tiě", "tāo dié"],
        answer: "tāo tiè"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: `'尴尬' 的拼音是什么？`,
        options: ["jiǎn gà", "jiàn gà", "jiān gà", "gān gà"],
        answer: "gān gà"
    }
]

export const Quizdata2 = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `下列哪个是正确的量词运用？`,
        options: ["一块蛋糕", "一个马", "一头人", "一只面包"],
        answer: "一块蛋糕"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `下列哪个是错误的量词运用？`,
        options: ["一盘棋", "一头牛", "一把米", "一堆水"],
        answer: "一堆水"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: `下列哪个是正确的量词运用？`,
        options: ["一个晚上", "一把瓶子", "一条笔", "一团水"],
        answer: "一个晚上"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `下列哪个是错误的量词运用？`,
        options: ["一杯水", "三片芝士", "五辆马", "一个答案"],
        answer: "五辆马"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `下列哪个是正确的量词运用？`,
        options: ["一只人", "两份晚餐", "四根盒子", "五副电视"],
        answer: "两份晚餐"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: `下列哪个是错误的量词运用？`,
        options: ["三匹狼", "两位贵宾", "三个房间", "四片计算机"],
        answer: "四片计算机"
    },
]
